现在是二零二三年天津市初中学业水平考试英语学科听力测试试听部分。
Hi, Lingling! What are you doing?
Hi, Peter! I'm reading a novel.
It's very funny.
Where did you get it?
I got it from a library.
Really? I just want to borrow some novels.
Where is the library?
It's on Fookung Road.
I'll take you there.
Thank you! Let's go!
you there. Thank you!
Let's go! Number 1.
嗨听部分到此结束。现在是二零二三年天津市初中学业水平考试英语学科听力测试时间，请考生做好准备。先请听听力测。是注意事项。一，听力理解共分三部分内容，从第一小题开始至第二十小题结束。二，全部听力测试每部分内容读两遍，请。考生边听边答题，将答案填涂在答题卡上。现在进行听力理解测试，请考生看试卷的第一页。一，听力理解。在下列每小题内，你将听到一个或两个句子，并看到供选择的三幅图画。找出与你所听句子内容相匹配的图画。
The dog is very lovely.
Number 2. We made a birthday cake yesterday.
Number 3. Linda wants to buy a shirt for her father.
Linda wants to buy a shirt for her father.
Number 4. Axe are healthy food.
They are good for our eyes.
下面你将听到十组对话，每组对话都有一个问题。根据对话内容，从每组所给的三个选项中找出能回答所提问题的最佳选项。
Number 5. What's the weather like?
It's cloudy. Number 6.
What color is your watch,
It's black. Number 7.
What's your favorite sport, Kate?
It's running. Number 8.
Where is the classroom building?
It's on the right of the gate.
Number 9. What are you going to do this weekend, I'm going to collect litter.
Number 10. What time does the chemistry lesson start?
At 8 o 'clock.
Number 11. When do you usually go to the park, Mike?
On Sundays. When do you usually go to the park, Mike?
On Sundays. Number 12.
Who will visit your parents next month, Tom?
My aunt. will visit your parents next month, Tom?
My aunt. Number 13.
How do you go to school every day, Lily?
By bike. But I went to school on foot this morning.
By bike. I went to school on foot this morning.
Number 14. I went to the bookshop to buy books yesterday.
What books did you buy?
I bought two Chinese books and three English books.
I went to the bookshop to buy books yesterday.
What books did you buy?
I bought two Chinese books and three English books.
Number 15. to to Hi, Mom.
听下面长对话或独白。每段长对话或独白后都有几个问题。从题中所给的三个选项中选出最佳选项。听下。下面一段材料，回答第十五至第十七题。
Hello, Jim. Where are you now?
I'm standing on the Great Wall of China and talking to you.
Really? That's great!
We are on a school trip.
At the moment, my classmates are taking photos.
Wonderful! Please buy some postcards of the Great Wall and send them to me by post.
Okay. I will buy some for you.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Jim.
Hi, Mom. Jim.
Where are you now?
I'm standing on the Great Wall of China and talking to you.
Really? That's great!
We are on a school trip.
At the moment, my classmates are taking photos.
Wonderful! Please buy some postcards of the Great Wall and send them to me by post.
Okay. I will buy some for you.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Jim.
Jim. to Hello, I'm Lihua.
听下面一段材料，回答第十八至第二十题。
I'm so happy to talk about my visit to Tianjin Museum.
It is the largest museum in our city.
We can enjoy lots of shows of traditional culture.
Last Friday, I visited Tianjin Museum.
I went there by underground and it took me half an hour to get there.
During my visit, I wrote down some important information so that I could complete a
report. I learned a lot about history and geography.
I think it's a very interesting experience.
Hello, I'm Lihua.
I'm so happy to talk about my visit to Tianjin Museum.
It is the largest museum in our city.
We can enjoy lots of shows of traditional culture.
Last Friday, I visited Tianjin Museum.
I went there by underground and it took me half an hour to get there.
During my visit, I wrote down some important information so that I could complete a
report. I learned a lot about history and geography.
I think it's a very interesting experience.
二零二三年天津市初中学业水平考试英语学科听力测试内容播放完毕。现在，请考生继续笔答其他部分试题。